<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Ali Miramirkhani</title>
        <link>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Ali Miramirkhani</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:18:18 +0430</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>We and the Body</title>
            <link>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/we-the-body/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:18:18 +0430</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/we-the-body/</guid>
            <description>There is this body that we inherited from evolution and there is us which is still an unknown entity. The fact here is that this physical body can be studied and discovered to see what we should do with it, how it works, how we might hurt it, and so on. There is some topic which we will discuss further how the functionality of it works and how we might have hurt it by our new and modern kind of living, the type of living which evolution didn&amp;rsquo;t make us for.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is this body that we inherited from evolution and there is us which is still an unknown entity. The fact here is that this physical body can be studied and discovered to see what we should do with it, how it works, how we might hurt it, and so on. There is some topic which we will discuss further how the functionality of it works and how we might have hurt it by our new and modern kind of living, the type of living which evolution didn&rsquo;t make us for.</p>
<p>The need for physical activity and where we invented excessive</p>
<p>How it metabolism works and why we need to go through special diets to advise our body goals</p>
<p>How we are connected to some sort of events and activity, like connecting to family, having sex, having a child, or being in love with someone, needs to be recognized, the act of self-comparison</p>
<p>Basically, whatever that you logically want and your body wouldn&rsquo;t let you have it with a direct path</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Skills</title>
            <link>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/skills/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:07:20 +0430</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/skills/</guid>
            <description>Earned skills vs. Built-in skill You may have experienced all sorts of insecurities and lack of soft and hard skills throughout your life and always wondered why you should have to try so hard to be confident in front of the crowd or why I need to be prepared to be a funny gut and why it takes me days to understand a math problem when my classmate already know the answer.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="earned-skills-vs-built-in-skill">Earned skills vs. Built-in skill</h2>
<p>You may have experienced all sorts of insecurities and lack of soft and hard skills throughout your life and always wondered why you should have to try so hard to be confident in front of the crowd or why I need to be prepared to be a funny gut and why it takes me days to understand a math problem when my classmate already know the answer. This thought might have driven you crazy considering how unfair it is that someone out there is born with or easily equipped with one skill or two while you should work really hard to be there.</p>
<p>However, we can deny how unfair these cases are but we should consider that earning a skill is much more rewarding than having it without fighting for it. The first is that will learn the functionality of that specific skill as a way to learn the whole thing and that gives us the privilege of even mastering it or changing its direction and dynamics for our benefit and empower us to teach it to other people and reach some level of skill that a born with the person could never do. It&rsquo;s like comparing old medication and the scientific way of medical approaches, if you have the medicine that works you may survive one or two occasions of sickness but are not guaranteed to pass through as you don&rsquo;t know the reasoning and science behind that medicine.</p>
<p>Additionally, as you have been on both sides of the river you can embrace and enjoy having an extra skill in your self and your mind always works in relative terms, and if you are gifted with something you may have never realized how lucky you are and will lose the joy.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Here I am</title>
            <link>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/examplepost/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:03:56 +0430</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://seiiedali.github.io/posts/examplepost/</guid>
            <description>Well now you get to know me I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if really works but lets give a try.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="well-now-you-get-to-know-me">Well now you get to know me</h1>
<p>I&rsquo;m not sure if really works but lets give a try.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
